Muhammad Irvan Hakim

irvanhakim.dev@gmail.com

+62 88806033610

linkedin.com/in/irvan-hakim

https://bakunya.pages.dev

Summary

I am Muhammad Irvan Hakim, an web developer with 2 years experience in professional and self-employed in non-profit organizations. In work, i often use technology stack as such as JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, and relational or non-relational database management. During my career, i have successfully developed web applications efficient and works well.

I have a good understanding of software design principles like architecture scalable and maintainable. In addition, I am known as a good learner and ready to continue honing my skills in this ever-evolving industry. I have good adaptability and able to work in a team or independently.

I believe that with a combination of experience, technical expertise, and high learning enthusiasm, I can make a positive contribution in web development.

Experience



💢 Frontend Web Developer

PT Gaia Solutions

Oct 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Handle task on frontend development as such as slicing to web page, build web using next.js, build backend service using hono.js, and manage services on cloudflare cloud platform.



🌃 Frontend Developer

PT. Lingkar Kreasi (Circle Creative)

Jun 2021 - Feb 2024 (2 years 9 months)

Handle task on frontend development as such as slicing to web page

Education



🏠 Universitas AMIKOM Yogyakarta

Associate Degree, Informatics 2021 - 2024

Skills

Laravel • React.js • MySQL • MongoDB • Node.js • JavaScript • TypeScript • Cloudflare • Front-End Development • Back-End Web Development